maykool.com 2014-03-28

# Privacy And Security

## **Privacy and Security**

**Privacy Policy on Maykool.com**

On Maykool.com, we take the protection for your Personal Information (such as name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; gender; language preference; and merchandise category preferences) very seriously.

We collect Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily and process it for the following purposes ("Purposes"):

•to complete transactions with you and manage your membership of our customer loyalty scheme where applicable;

•to guide you the latest market trend;

•to understand and analyse our sales, and your needs and preferences;

•to develop, enhance, market and provide products and services to meet your needs;

•to enable you to participate in promotions and contests;

•to enable you to participate in customer research or focus groups;

•to process exchanges or product returns;

•to improve our competitiveness and service,

•to respond to requests or complaints.

Maykool.com will respect your privacy and will pay attention to your online safety. We will record a variety of information from your visit to our site in order to provide the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates for you. You will see the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. All of this information which we made is in order to protect your privacy better.

At first, thank you for accessing the website ("Site") of Maykool.com, Limited. ("Maykool.com," that's us). Your privacy will be respected and your personal information will be protected. If you want to know more information, you can read our privacy notice.

Though this privacy notice, you can know that how we collect, use, (and under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. Finally, you will know your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information with the privacy notice. You accept the practices described in this Notice by visiting our site.

You can apply this Privacy Notice only in this Site. So for our offline collection of your personal information, this privacy policy is not necessary. You will see the detail below. The content or privacy practices on any non-Maykool.com website to which this Site links or that links to this Site is not our responsibility.

**Data Security**

Maykool.com incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions through this Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate. For example, when you visit our Site, you access servers that are kept in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall.

While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline.

**Can I Trust Maykool.com**

1:What is the difference between Maykool.com and other Chinese suppliers

You're right to be cautious to have any doubts about importing from China. With some key information about Maykool.com, you will have more confidence in starting out with your new China Wholesale supplier:   

Our Maykool.com is different from most Chinese export companies which have minimum order restriction. From a wide selection of the latest released products, you can make an order at any amount, even a piece of sample. You're committed to any large orders after you have test products and find out about the details of importing from Maykool.com. For avoiding having to share any of your financial information and having total buyer protection, you can pay by credit card through PayPal.  

When you place an order, we will offer the English speaking staff to assist you friendly. During this period, you can get the full information about the products which you want to buy. 

We will pack your goods very carefully. At the same time, we can label and accompanied the packages correctly with the paperwork for smooth clearance through your country's Customs.

2:Why you can trust Maykool.com

When you use PayPal to pay for your order on Maykool, PayPal's money back guarantees will protect you and there is no need to share any of your confidential financial details with Maykool.

The Maykool website is certified "Secure Site" by VeriSign and is also verified by ValidatedSite.

3:Is it safe to shop at Maykool.com

Thank you for accessing the website ("Site") of Maykool. At Maykool.com, we guarantee you that your personal information remains strictly confidential. We do not save your payment information in our data store. Payments made through PayPal are processed by PayPal Company. It is considered to be secure and trustworthy. We also do not disclose your information to third parties. For more details, please see our privacy notice.
